http://www.waynecounty.com/county/privacy.aspx

Commissioners
Tim Killeen (Dist. 1)
Jewel Ware (Dist. 2)
Martha G. Scott (Dist. 3)
Ilona Varga (Dist. 4)
Irma Clark-Coleman (Dist. 5)
Monique Baker McCormick (Dist. 6)
Alisha Bell (Dist. 7)
David M. Knezek Jr.
(Dist. 8)
Terry Marecki (Dist. 9)
Melissa Daub (Dist. 10)
Al Haidous (Dist. 11)
Glenn S. Anderson (Dist. 12)
Sam Baydoun (Dist. 13)
Raymond Basham (Dist. 14)
Joseph Palamara (Dist. 15)
Archived Election Information
August 9, 2018 Primary Election Results - Precinct by Precinct
February 27, 2007 Special School Election Results
Vote!!! 2020!
Public Integrity Unit
Prosecutor's Auto Theft Unit (PATU)
WCPO Staff Speaking Invitation Form
What is a Prosecutor?
Wayne County Blunt Facts
Michigan State University Extension (MSU-E)
Environmental Regulations
North Branch Ecorse Creek Report (PDF)
Rouge River Project Report (PDF)
Privacy Policy
Share:
Privacy Policy
The information contained in this website is and/or may be protected, confidential, sensitive in nature, subject to the attorney client, attorney work product or other privilege, and intended solely for the use of the public addressee(s). The use, dissemination, distribution, publication or action in reliance on any of the information contained in this communication is strictly prohibited. In the event of any unauthorized access to, or use of the information contained in this medium, the County of Wayne hereby reserves all rights and remedies available to it under applicable federal and state laws. The County of Wayne shall be deemed to be held harmless from any and all fines, penalties and assessments, including attorney fees, and expenses, levied as a result of the unauthorized use, dissemination, distribution, publication or action in reliance on any of the information contained in this communication.The information contained in this Website is current (to the best of our ability) as of its original March 31, 2004 release date. The information is updated frequently based upon the needs and feedback from county departments, divisions, agencies, and municipalities. The purpose of this site is to serve the general public and is not intended to endorse private or partisan political concerns, or those of commercial enterprises.Wayne County Terms Of Use And Linking PolicyThe Wayne County web portal is owned and operated by the Wayne County government and provided as a service to the public. The use of the content, images and logos on the Wayne County web portal on any other web site or networked computer environment is prohibited.Some of the materials on the web portal may be saved on any single personal computer for personal, non-commercial use only. All copyrighted material and other means of proprietary or copyright identification must be kept intact and unmodified. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for purposes not granted by the Wayne County is a violation of Wayne County's copyright and other proprietary rights.Wayne County Links to Other SitesWayne County provides links to other organizations through this website. These links are provided for additional information as a service to the public. In providing these links, Wayne County does not endorse the content, products, services or viewpoints expressed by these external sites. Once you leave the Wayne County website and link to an external site, the Wayne County Internet policies no longer apply and you will be subject to the new site's policies.Wayne County provides links to the following types of organizations:Links to Other Governmental Units & Educational Institutions - Wayne County provides links to other federal, state, and local governmental units that provide additional services and information that users of this site may find of interest.Links to Private Organizations - Wayne County provides links to private organizations if these organizations offer services that complement the information or services offered by Wayne County. The determination of whether to establish links to a private organization's website is made on a case-by-case basis. Links to Non-Profit Organizations - Wayne County provides links to non-profit organizations that users of this site may find of interest. The determination of whether to establish links to non-profit organizations is made on a case-by-case basis.Privacy StatementWayne County maintains this web site as a public service. The following is the privacy policy regarding this site.The Collection and Use of InformationWayne County has links to other web sites outside of county government. When you link to one of these sites, Wayne County cannot control their use of cookies and this privacy policy will not apply.Information Sharing and DisclosureWayne County will only send personal information about you to others when:We have your consent to share the information; or we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; or we are authorized to do so by law (e.g., to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, or to requests pursuant to a statute requiring or permitting disclosure such as the Freedom of Information Act. MCL 15.231, et seq.: MSA 4.1801(1) et seq.)Changes to this Privacy PolicyWayne County may amend this policy from time to time. Wayne County will prominently display on this website any substantial change in the way we use your personal information.Wayne County Security PolicyWayne County Department of Technology, as developer and manager of the Wayne County portal, has taken a number of steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information that is maintained in agency computer systems. These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, ensure the integrity of information that is transmitted between users of e-government applications and the county, and to provide reasonable protection of private information that is in our possession.For security purposes and to make sure this service remains available to all users,Wayne County uses special software programs for monitoring and auditing network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise to cause damage to this government computer system. Wayne County also uses industry-standard software tools to control access to specific applications and services and to protect data that is transmitted electronically between users and the county. These programs help us identify someone attempting to tamper with this website.WARNING: If security monitoring reveals possible evidence of criminal activity, information pertaining to such activity may be provided to law enforcement officials.Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on the Wayne County portal or its composite web sites are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and Title 18 U.S.C. Sec.1001 and 1030.The information contained in this policy statement should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided via the Wayne County portal or the web sites of individual departments, divisions, or agencies.Wayne County collects information from you under the following circumstances:Information Collected AutomaticallySome information is collected from you automatically when you view these pages and download information. This may include your Internet Protocol address assigned by your Internet Service Provider, domain name and the type of browser and operating system you used, the date and time you accessed this site, the pages you requested and visited, and the site you linked from to reach Wayne County. We use this type of information to statistically measure site traffic and to improve the web site. The information is not reviewed on an individual basis but is aggregated with other users for comparison purposes.Information Voluntarily SubmittedAdditional information may be collected from you if you opt-in or voluntarily provide it in order to fulfill a request for on-line services. Wayne County uses the information you voluntarily provide to tailor our site to your needs and preferences and to provide the on-line services you are requesting. The type of information we collect will vary with the service being sought and may include your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, social security or federal identification number, credit card number and expiration date, and/or driver license number.CookiesIn order to customize your browsing experience, Wayne County may use "cookies". Cookies allow information to change as you navigate through the pages of a web site. Two types of cookies can be used, "session-only" and "persistent". Wayne County uses cookies in the following ways: If you wish to access information, Wayne County uses session-only cookies to reserve some storage on your computer in order to take your query and pass it along to the page that will serve up the information you request. The session-only cookies are erased either during web browser operation or after your web browser is shut down.If you wish to conduct on-line transactions but do not want to personalize the site, Wayne County uses session-only cookies to process your request. The type of information voluntarily submitted to fulfill your request varies by transaction and may include your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, social security or federal identification number, credit card number and expiration date, and/or driver license number.If you choose to register with any of Wayne County or it's affiliated sites as a user or to personalize the site and wish to be remembered, Wayne County uses permanent cookies that remain on your computer's hard drive as small text files. These permanent cookies allow Wayne County to recognize you when you return to our site. When you register with Wayne County, we ask you to identify yourself by your name and email address. This allows Wayne County to customize the presentation of information for you based upon what you have asked for and/or voluntarily provided during previous visits. Wayne County only uses permanent cookies with the permission of the user.If you choose to register with Wayne County to personalize the site but do not wish to be remembered, Wayne County uses session cookies that are destroyed when you close your browser.
Warren C. Evans
Wayne County Executive
Email
(313) 224-0286
Stay Connected
Wayne County, Michigan, All Rights Reserved. Privacy Statement, Legal Notices and Terms of Use
Location Map
Document Viewer
